Pankaj Kushwaha

Senior Software Developer

Phone: +91 9560248029

Email: pankajkushwaha1990@gmail.com

Address: H-52, Brij Vihar, Chapraula, Ghaziabad

Senior Software Developer with 6+ years of experienced in developing applications and solutions for a wide range of corporate and public sector clients and having the enthusiasm and ambition to complete projects to the highest standard. Looking for a suitable developer position with a ambitious & exciting company.

RELEVANT SKILLS

PHP	MYSQL	MONGODB	LARAVEL	CODEIGNITOR
REST API	HTML	CSS	JQUERY	BOOTSTRAP
Javascript	React			

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Catabatic Private Limited / Noida

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER June 2021 – Present

Masters India Private Limited / Noida

PHP DEVELOPER Dec 2018 – March 2021

SNT InfoTech / Ghaziabad

PHP DEVELOPER

July 2017 – Aug 2018

Gennext IT Solution / Noida

PHP DEVELOPER

July 2015 – July 2017

PROJECT

- Eudora (Travel Package Booking)
- Tata Advance Systems
- Spectra (Internet Service Provider)
- Autotax (GST Billing and Compliance Solution)
- Pinneria (Business Directory)
- SRCC (Placement Cell)
- Bizzduniya (B2B Marketplace)
- Finding Holidays

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

Mahatma Gandhi Mission College Of Engineering / Noida

B.tech. Computer Science

June 2015

10+2 / UP Board *PCM*

June 2009

AWARDS

1st Prize Winner Of Mozilla Firefox

Conducted By College

3rd Prize Winner Of Code-E-Thon

Conducted By College

OTHERS SKILLS

Version Control

GIT, SVN

Tools

SUBLIME, POSTMAN, FILEZILLA, CPANEL, PUTTY

Platform

WINDOWS, LINUX

Payment Gateway Integration

HDFC, PAYU, PAYPAL, ROZARPAY

API Integration

FACEBOOK API, GOOGLE MAP API, SMS API, EMAIL SMTP

Website Library Integration

HIGHCHART, GROCERY CRUD, DATATABLE